designerpages.com 2011-06-29

# Designer Pages: Privacy Policy

Last Updated: March 2011

This policy covers eight sections, and you can jump to each by selecting the links below: 

Introduction  
1\. The Type of Information We Collect and Use  
2\. The Way We Use Information  
3\. Cookies and Web Beacons  
4\. Your Ability to Edit or Delete Account Information  
5\. Confidentiality and Security  
6\. Children Under 13  
7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy  
8\. Your Consent  

**Introduction**

Designer Pages Online LLC ("We," "Our," or "the Company") respects the privacy of your personal information and provides the following explanation of how We treat personal information that We collect and receive when you use Our website and services, including any of Our mobile apps, such as the Showrooms app (the "Site" or the "Services"). The type and amount of information We collect about you varies according to how you use Our Services. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that We do not own or control, or to practices of people that We do not employ or manage. 

**The Type of Information We Collect and Use**

Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable and that is not otherwise publicly available, such as your address, email address, and phone number. We may collect personal information when you register with Our Site, when you use certain products and Services, when you visit Our Site or the websites of certain third parties, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. For example: 

  * When you register on Our Site, We collect and store your email address, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. We may also collect and store information We are able to gather about you through social media and networking websites, including but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. Once you register with the Company and sign into Our Services, you are not anonymous to the Company.

  * If you use Our location-enabled Services, We may collect and reveal to the public your physical location, including but not limited to your GPS data, in addition to any additional comments and information you may post.

  * We collect information about your interactions with the Company and with some third parties whose information you have viewed through our Site, such as advertisers, manufacturers and showroom owners, including wholesale distributors and retailers ("Third Parties"). We may share the information We collect about you with such Third Parties.

  * We automatically gather general statistical information from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the pages you request. We use this data to determine how much users use parts of Our Site so We can improve Our Site and report this data to Third Parties in the aggregate to provide information on designer behavior trends. We may also use and report individual data, including personally identifiable data, to Third Parties that you interact with using Our Site.

  * We may combine information about you that We have with information We obtain from Third Parties, social media and networking websites, including but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, and other companies.

The information We may collect is categorized as follows: 

  * Application Information- information you provide to the Company through Our Site and through other means. Examples include your name, address, and telephone number.

  * Information from Outside Sources- information from outside sources regarding your background and other relationships. Examples include your public record information available on social media and networking websites.

Back to top

**The Way We Use Information**

We generally use information for the following purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to provide you with the Services, to improve the Services, to contact you, to conduct research, and to provide reporting for Third Parties. In addition: 

  * We provide your name, email address, company and search information to Third Parties. These Third Parties may use your personal information to communicate with you about their offers and offers from Our Company if they choose to do so. 

  * We may use information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce the Terms of Service. At times, We may review status or activity of multiple users to do so. We may disclose or access information whenever We believe in good faith that the law so requires or if We otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain and improve Our Services. 

  * We may provide targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. By interacting with or viewing an ad, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. We may provide personal information to an advertiser if you interact with or view a targeted ad.

We may send you certain communications relating to Our Services, such as service announcements and administrative notices. We may also send you Our email newsletter and other communications relevant to the Site. You may unsubscribe to the email newsletter or select certain categories of newsletters you wish to receive from the Company by visiting our Newsletter Preferences page. You may also unsubscribe to our email newsletter by following the instructions contained in the communication. 

Back to top

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

As part of Our Services, We use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use web beacons to access Our cookies inside and outside Our Site and in connection with Our Services. We may also use web beacons to determine whether you have visited a link on Our Site. In some instances, We allow other companies that show advertisements on some of Our pages to use their own cookies, which are subject to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to read their privacy policies before responding to their offers. 

Back to top

**Your Ability to Edit or Delete Account Information**

You can edit your account information at any time through normal updating methods. To delete your account, please email the Company at [accounts@designerpages.com](mailto:accounts@designerpages.com). Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in Our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

Back to top

**Confidentiality and Security**

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. Further, We limit access to personal information about you to employees who We believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide the Services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

Back to top

**Children Under 13**

We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who access Our Site, and so We carry out the same privacy policy for individuals of all ages. If a child has provided the Company with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact the Company to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. 

Back to top

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes to Our Privacy Policy will be communicated through Our Site. We will also contact registered users by email when and if significant changes are made to this Privacy Policy. 

Back to top

**Your Consent**

By using Our Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner We describe. 

Back to top
